Your health is a true guarantee of many things:
fitness claims, doctor consultations, health and,
if required, hospitalization.
So, don't choose just one health policy;
choose a wellness partner. Lombard's
health benefit plan covers every step of your health journey, from preventive care to
doctor appointments to hospitalization.
It
is truly a partner and offers numerous benefits,
such as sum insured restoration up to Rs. 3 crore,
health check-up bonuses,
individual and floater plans,
maternity lab coverage for the entire family.
This policy lets you choose cover based on your and your family's
health needs.
It
also has a unique feature called "Same Insured Restore," which
covers the same illness for which the individual was already
hospitalized. This means
that if the sum insured and the
guarantee accumulated bonus are exhausted due to claims, you will
get back a sum insured equal to 100% of the sum assured for the particular policy year for all members in the policy, subject to any additional admissible claim. The
Guaranteed Century Bonus feature means
that the accumulated bonus is not affected even in case of a claim.
Additionally, a maximum of 9 individuals can be covered under a single policy.  There is an
option to insure
yourself, husband and wife, 3 children,
both parents and in-laws and also
avail the benefit of health check-up.
ICICI Lombard will cover the
cost of health check-up up to 1% of the sum insured per policy
subject to a maximum of Rs 10,000.
The plan also offers maternity and newborn coverage.
Maternity cover is available up to 10% of the sum insured in three
spreads subject to a maximum of Rs 10 lakh.
Give your healthcare the benefits it deserves with ICICI Lombard's Health Advantage Plan. Also avail our
drug information and approval process and 24/7
customer support. We
are your partner in healthcare
[Music]